mobitel.lk 2019-12-14

# Mobitel Privacy Policy | Mobitel

####  Privacy Policy

There are services offered on Mobitel's web sites whereby you may subscribe to, by providing to us your personal information as requested. Personal information refers to all and any information relating to you obtained by us in the course of and as a result of the provision of the services by us. Such personal information could include your name, mailing address, phone number and e-mail address.

By submitting material to any of our servers, for example, by e-mail or via the Mobitel World Wide Web pages, you agree that:

(a) the material will not contain any item that is unlawful or otherwise unfit for publication;

(b) you will use reasonable efforts to scan and remove any viruses or other contaminating or destructive features before submitting any material; and

(c) you own the material or have the unlimited right to provide it to us and Mobitel may publish the material free of charge and/or incorporate it or any concepts described in it in our products without accountability or liability

(d) you agree not to take action against Mobitel in relation to material that you submit and you agree to indemnify Mobitel if any third party takes action against us in relation to the material you submit. By providing Mobitel with this information, you have given Mobitel your consent to use your personal information for lawful purposes, including but not limited to, providing assistance to law enforcement or other government agencies, to our research companies, for joint promotional activities, for managing bad debt and preventing fraud; otherwise kindly inform us in writing to withdraw your consent.

Mobitel does not and cannot review the content posted by users on its site and is not responsible for such content. Mobitel may at any time at its discretion remove any content posted by users.  

####  Privacy Policy for e-news letter

Mobitel does not share your contact details (i.e. e-mail) with any other.

The information contained in the Mobitel website is for general information purposes only. Mobitel takes reasonable measures to ensure the accuracy of the information. However, if information is found to be inaccurate please feel free to contact us for verification of information on 0712755777.  

Mobitel endeavours to keep the website functioning smoothly. However, Mobitel takes no responsibility and disclaims all liability for the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond its control.
